flash-design-marketing.com 2004-06-05

# Russian Brides Link: Policy Privacy to order Russian Brides contact info

  |   |   | 

### Russian Brides Link Collects Information from You

**Russian Brides Link.com** collects personal information when you visit Russian Brides Link pages to order contact info of Russian brides or dating services, when you fill out the order form we ask you for information such as your name, email address, birth date, zip code, and personal credit card info.   
Russian Brides Link.com also utilizes cookies to keep track of your order and to personalize your experience at Russian Brides Link.com. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to track your order history. 

Russian Brides Link collects information about your transactions with us, including information about your use of dating services that we offer. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Russian Brides Link cookie information, and the page you request. 

### How Russian Brides Link uses Your information

We use your IP address   
\- to help diagnose problems with our server,   
\- to administer our web site and   
\- collect regional demographic information.  
We use information for the following general purposes:   
\- to customize the advertising and content you see,   
\- fulfill your requests for products and services,   
\- improve our services,   
\- contact you,   
\- conduct research.  

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Russian Brides Link does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

> o We provide the information to trusted partners: financial service providers such as banks, who work on behalf of or with Russian Brides Link under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Russian Brides Link provide transactions to Russian Brides Link.   
>  o We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;   
>  o We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Russian Brides Link 's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.   
>  o We transfer information about you if Russian Brides Link is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Russian Brides Link will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Your Credit Card Details

We DO NOT sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permishion. We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user should provide contact information (like name and e-mail) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date etc.). This information is collected by 1st International Marriage network, our credit card processor, which provides highly secure payment processing for Russian-Brides-Link.com, and used for billing purposes and to fill customer's order. **Please note that you will be billed by 1st International Marriage Network.**

Credit card information is encrypted using the SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) protocol implemented by Netscape and Internet Explorer.  

### Confidentiality and Security

· We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.   
· We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.   
· Russian Brides Link has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order confirmation-form, that you'll see after submited order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.  

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please can contact us at our address:   

### Main Office

1st International  
2665 N. Atlantic Ave. #222  
Daytona Beach, FL 32118  
USA

Toll free phone: (800) 676-9149  
Outside US call: 1-(386) 441-0321  
Toll free fax: 1-800-211-8415  
Outside US fax: 1-305-946-2479

|   |   |
